Guide to the Time Inc. People Publishing and Business Records 1973-2003 MS 3009-RG 27
New-York Historical Society
Time Inc. People Publishing and Business Records
1973-2003
New-York Historical Society
Time, inc.
MS 3009-RG 27
80.35 Linear feet in 82 record cartons
With the first issue launched on on March 4, 1974, People was one of the first publications coming out of the Magazine Development Group later transitioning into its own department. The People Publishing and Business Records contain records from offices and staff from the publishing and business side of the magazine, not the editorial side. Staff represented include Publisher Richard Durrell, Assistant Publisher Charlotte Schiff-Jones, Associate Consumer Marketing Director John Hartig, Director of Marketing Services Chuck Lund, and Magazine Development Group Marketing Director Mal Ochs.
Biographical / Historical
People magazine was launched as a newsstand-only publication on March 4, 1974, with Richard Durrell as founding publisher. Before joining People, Durrell worked in advertising for both Life and Time magazines, including a position as Life's Assistant Publisher. People was created under the Magazine Development Group, divesting and becoming its own department by 1978. The Magazine Development Group, Time Inc.'s in-house publishing idea think tank, had previously successfully launched Money magazine in 1972.
The magazine exceeded sales of one million copies per issue by July 1974 due to Richard Durrell creating a distribution network within Time Inc., known as Time Distribution Services (TDS). TDS worked with and eventually replaced the distributor Select Magazines Inc. and focused on market research to improve sales tactics.
For the majority of Time Inc.'s existence, the company maintained a strict separation of editorial from the publishing and business side of each magazine, colloquially called the separation of "church" (editorial) and "state" (publishing). Publishing and Business Management includes the publisher, general manager, business manager, advertising sales, marketing services, letters, circulation, and public relations. The editorial side reported up to the editor-in-chief and the publishing/business side reported up to the corporate business executive which was the president prior to 1960 and the chief executive officer after. Henry Luce structured Time Inc. this way so that the business side could not (in theory) influence the editorial content of the publications. For example, the advertising sales people could not interfere with a magazine's decision to run an article on the dangers of cigarette smoking, even though it might mean losing millions of dollars in tobacco ads.
Citations:
Elson, Robert T., Curtis Prendergast, and Geoffrey Colvin. Time Inc.; the Intimate History of a Publishing Enterprise, 1960-1980. New York: Atheneum, 1985.
Hooper, Bill. Email to Holly Deakyne, 10 June 2016.
Scope and Contents
The People Publishing and Business Records contain records from offices and staff from the publishing and business side of the magazine, not the editorial side. Staff represented include Publisher Richard Durrell, Assistant Publisher Charlotte Schiff-Jones, Associate Consumer Marketing Director John Hartig, Director of Marketing Services Chuck Lund, and Magazine Development Group Marketing Director Mal Ochs. Records include correspondence, memorandum, advertising and marketing records, poll results, statistical computer analysis reports, convention information, People magazine development materials, and information on the short-lived 1978 Time-Life Films People television series. Includes records from when People operated under the Magazine Development Group before becoming its own department.
Arrangement Note
The record group is currently organized in six series:
Series I. Publisher Richard Durrell Files
Series II. Assistant Publisher Charlotte Schiff-Jones Files
Series III. Marketing Files
Series IV. Advertising Files
Series V. Public Affairs Records
Series VI. General Files
Access Restrictions
Open to qualified researchers with the exception of restricted materials. Restricted materials include contracts and agreements; records with personally identifiable information; and records with mold issues. Restricted materials are located in box R42. Box R43 contains materials restricted due to mold.
Unreformatted audiovisual material in the collection is not accessible.
Materials are stored offsite and advance notice is required for use.
Related Archival Materials Note
This finding aid relates to just one record group of the Time Inc. Records. For information about the other record groups and for overall information about the archives, please see the Guide to the Time Inc. Records (MS 3009). The Henry Luce Papers (MS 3014) were acquired with the Time Inc. Records. The collection of books acquired with the records are cataloged as the Time Inc. Reference Library.
Information about the history of People and additional records from the publishing and business offices can be found in the Time Inc. Subject Files (MS 3009-RG 1) and the Time Inc. Annex Files (MS 3009-RG 39). Records from the editorial offices are in the Time Inc. People Editorial Records (MS 3009-RG 10).
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Time Inc. in 2015.
American periodicals -- History; Corporations -- New York (State); Corporation records.; Organization files.; Periodicals -- Publishing.; Publishers and publishing -- New York (State) -- New York.; Time, inc. -- Archives.; Time, inc. -- History.
- Series I. Publisher Richard Durrell Files, 1973-1983; 56.25 Linear feet in 57 record cartons
  Biographical / Historical
  Richard Durrell joined Time Inc. as a circulation newsstand representative following graduation from the University of Minnesota in 1948. He worked in advertising for both Life and Time magazines, including a position as Life's Assistant Publisher. He was instrumental in the launch of People Magazine as its founding publisher in 1974. The magazine was launched as a newsstand-only publication on March 4, 1974, and exceeded sales of one million copies per issue by July 1974 due to Durrell creating a distribution network within Time Inc., known as Time Distribution Service (TDS). TDS worked with and eventually replaced Select Magazines Inc., Time Inc.'s previous distributor, and focused on market research to improve sales tactics. He was a vice president of Time Inc. and retired from the company as People publisher in 1984.
  Citations:
  Creswell, Julie. "Richard J. Durrell, First Publisher of People Magazine, Dies at 82." The New York Times. March 08, 2008. Accessed November 27, 2018. https://www.nytimes.com/2008/03/08/business/media/08durrell.html.
  Elson, Robert T., Curtis Prendergast, and Geoffrey Colvin. Time Inc.; the Intimate History of a Publishing Enterprise, 1960-1980. New York: Atheneum, 1985.
  Scope and Contents
  Materials are from Richard Durrell's position at People and also within the advertising industry (see: convention materials and speeches).
  Arrangement
  Arranged into two subseries:
  Subseries I.A. Magazine Development Files
  Subseries I.B. Subject Files
  - Subseries I.A. Magazine Development Files, 1973-1975; 1 Linear feet in 1 record carton
    Materials were collected from Tony Cox by Richard Durrell to be kept as reference on the development of People magazine. Font tests, congratulatory correspondence from collegues in and outside of Time Inc., and research on other magazines are included.
    In original order.
    - ANA: October 1973 (RDJ Letter) (Offsite-box 2947, Folder 1)
    - Bonuses, 1973 (Offsite-box 2947, Folder 2)
    - Clips: People, 1973 (Offsite-box 2947, Folder 3)
    - Comments on People, 1973 (Offsite-box 2947, Folder 4)
    - Compton: Promotions, etc, 1973-1975 (Offsite-box 2947, Folder 5)
    - Congratulatory Notes: Outside, 1973 (Offsite-box 2947, Folder 6)
    - Congratulatory Notes: Time Inc., 1973 (Offsite-box 2947, Folder 7)
      Includes audiovisual material:
      1 phonograph record (45 rpm); 7 in. Label on side 1: "Barbara Streisand, 'People'". Label on side 2: "Barbara Streisand, 'Secondhand Rose'". Label on container: "Columbia Hall of Fame Records. '10/18/73, Dick-- People who are people-people are the loveliest people in the world. Congrats, Dick Maylander'".
    - Facsimile Covers, 1973 (Offsite-box 2947, Folder 8)
    - Launch Presentation, 1973 (Offsite-box 2947, Folder 9)
    - Legal, 1973 (Offsite-box 2947, Folder 11)
    - Legal: Logo and Other People Magazines, 1973-1974 (Offsite-box 2947, Folder 12)
    - Launch Presentation, 1973 (Offsite-box 2947, Folder 10)
    - Memoranda: Larsen, Roy, 1973 (Offsite-box 2947, Folder 13)
    - Memoranda: Miscellaneous, 1973 (Offsite-box 2947, Folder 14)
    - Merchandising, 1973 (Offsite-box 2947, Folder 15)
    - National Enquirer, 1973 (Offsite-box 2947, Folder 16)
    - National Star, 1973-1974 (Offsite-box 2947, Folder 17)
    - People: Original P & L Statements: Launch March 1, 1974, 1973 (Offsite-box 2947, Folder 18)
    - People Pre-Publishing, 1973-1974 (Offsite-box 2947, Folder 19)
    - People #2 Research, 1973 (Offsite-box 2947, Folder 20)
    - People Test: Expenses, Questionnaires, Etc., 1973 (Offsite-box 2947, Folder 21)
    - People Typeface: Century, 1973 (Offsite-box 2947, Folder 22)
    - People Typeface: Helvetica, 1973 (Offsite-box 2947, Folder 23)
    - People Typeface: Helvetica Unjustified, 1973 (Offsite-box 2947, Folder 24)
    - People Typeface: Remington, 1973 (Offsite-box 2947, Folder 25)
    - Permissions, 1973 (Offsite-box 2947, Folder 26)
    - Rate Protection Plan, 1973 (Offsite-box 2947, Folder 27)
    - Reactions, 1973 (Offsite-box 2947, Folder 28)
  - Subseries I.B. Subject Files, 1973-1983; 55.25 Linear feet in 56 record cartons
    Materials include: memoranda from sales staff and People staff, correspondence, advertising research, advertising numbers, Time Distribution Services (TDS) files, correspondence with advertising agency Young & Rubicam, convention materials, golf trip information, speeches, branch office information for end of year, People development materials, copies of People magazine, and information on luncheon or dinner engagements.
    Notable correspondents include: Dick Stolley, Pat Ryan, Hugh Sidey, Hedley Donovan, Art Keylor, and Erik Thorkilsen.
    Arranged by year, then alphabetically within year. People branch office materials are filed at the end of each year.
    - 18 Month Plan: People, 1974 (Offsite-box 2947, Folder 29)
    - Advertising Marketing Strategy, 1974 (Offsite-box 2947, Folder 30)
    - Announcement Ad, 1974 (Offsite-box 2947, Folder 31)
    - Announcements 1973-1974 (Offsite-box 2947, Folder 32)
    - Bios, 1974 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 1)
    - Budgets: General, 1974 (Offsite-box 2947, Folder 33)
    - Cambridge Marketing Group, 1974 (Offsite-box 2947, Folder 34)
    - Circulation, 1974 (Offsite-box 2947, Folder 35)
    - Cole, Monger, Waterhouse, 1974 (Offsite-box 2947, Folder 36)
    - Comments: Publicity (Extras), 1974 (Offsite-box 2947, Folder 37)
    - Conventions: American Association of Advertising Agencies: May 15-18, 1974 (Offsite-box 2947, Folder 38)
    - Conventions: NAFC: Las Vegas: October 20-23, 1974 (Offsite-box 2947, Folder 39)
    - Conventions: Housing Conference: Lyford Cay: November 6-10, 1974 (Offsite-box 2947, Folder 40)
    - Cover: Policy, Positions, 1974 (Offsite-box 2947, Folder 41)
    - CPM, 1974 (Offsite-box 2947, Folder 42)
    - Critiques on People: By Agencies, Etc., 1974 (Offsite-box 2947, Folder 43)
    - Detroit, 1974 (Offsite-box 2947, Folder 44)
    - Ideas for People: From Outside, 1974 (Offsite-box 2947, Folder 45)
    - Launch Party: February 25-27, 1974 (Offsite-box 2948, Folder 1)
    - Letters: Miscellaneous, 1974 (Offsite-box 2948, Folder 2)
    - Letters: To Lists from Richard Durrell, 1974 (Offsite-box 2948, Folder 3)
    - Lists: Dummy Issue, 1974 (Offsite-box 2948, Folder 4)
    - "Magic Of People" Presentation: Doug Henning Lunches: October 8-10, 1974 (Offsite-box 2948, Folder 5)
    - Marketing Plan, 1974 (Offsite-box 2948, Folder 6)
    - Memoranda: Coffey, Richard, 1973-1974 (Offsite-box 2948, Folder 7)
    - Memoranda: Keylor, Art, 1974 (Offsite-box 2948, Folder 8)
    - Memoranda: Furst, Austin, 1974 (Offsite-box 2948, Folder 9)
    - Memoranda: Larsen, Roy, 1974 (Offsite-box 2948, Folder 10)
    - Memoranda: Miscellaneous, 1974 (Offsite-box 2948, Folder 11)
    - Memoranda: Posthorn, Stan, 1974 (Offsite-box 2948, Folder 12)
    - Memoranda: Stolley, Dick, 1974 (Offsite-box 2948, Folder 13)
    - Memoranda: Sutton, Kelso, 1974 (Offsite-box 2948, Folder 14)
    - Memoranda: Thomas, Dick, 1974 (Offsite-box 2948, Folder 15)
    - Memoranda: Valk, Garry, 1974 (Offsite-box 2948, Folder 16)
    - Monthly Reports to Art Keylor, 1974 (Offsite-box 2948, Folder 17)
    - Orient Express Showing: November 21, 1974 (Offsite-box 2948, Folder 18)
    - People Magazines, 1974 (Offsite-box 2948, Folder 19-20)
    - Personnel, 1974 (Offsite-box 2948, Folder 21)
    - Photographers: Use of Pictures, Etc., 1974 (Offsite-box 2948, Folder 22)
    - Postal Rates, 1974 (Offsite-box 2948, Folder 23)
    - Promotion: General and Advertising, 1974 (Offsite-box 2948, Folder 24)
    - Publicity: Print: Letters, Etc., 1974 (Offsite-box 2948, Folder 25)
    - Pub Letter, 1974 (Offsite-box 2948, Folder 26)
    - Publisher's Information Bureau, 1974 (Offsite-box 2948, Folder 27)
    - Publisher's Report Letter: 17 Weeks: August 12, 1974 (Offsite-box 2948, Folder 28)
    - Research, 1974 (Offsite-box 2948, Folder 29)
    - Screening: The Great Gatsby, 1974 (Offsite-box 2948, Folder 30)
    - SDRS, 1974 (Offsite-box 2948, Folder 31)
    - Select Magazines, Incorporated, 1974 (Offsite-box 2948, Folder 32)
    - Select Magazines: Store Checks: Letters To and From, 1974 (Offsite-box 2948, Folder 33)
    - Select Magazines: Wholesalers, 1974 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 1)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Durrell, Dick, 1974 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 2)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Thomas, Dick, 1974 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 3)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Miscellaneous, 1974 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 4)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Posthorn, Stan, 1974 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 5)
    - Speeches, 1974 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 6)
    - Speeches: Others, 1974 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 7)
    - Speeches: Overseas Press Club, 1974 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 8)
    - Study: Study of Target Public Attitudes Toward People Magazine and Reactions to Specific Editorial Dimensions, 1974 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 9)
    - Study: Top Advertisers and Agency People Magazine as a Vehicle for Advertising, 1974 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 10)
    - Subscription: Pricing, Etc., 1974 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 11)
    - Swaps: Trades, Etc., 1974 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 12)
    - Syndication, 1974 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 13)
    - Syndication: Air, 1974 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 14)
    - Syndication: Print, 1974 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 15)
    - Testimonial Ad, 1974 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 16)
    - Tests: Sales, Etc., 1974 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 17)
    - Trendex, 1974 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 18)
    - UPC (Universal Product Code), 1974 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 19)
    - Weekly Reports To Art Keylor, 1974 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 20)
    - Year End Double Issue, 1974 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 21)
    - Young & Rubicam: Promotion, People Advertising, 1974 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 22)
    - ActMedia, 1975 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 23)
    - Advertising Complaints (Reproductions, Etc.), 1975 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 24)
    - Ad Director's Letter, 1975 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 25)
    - Ad Records, 1975 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 26)
    - Airline: Subscriptions, 1975 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 27)
    - Airport: Sales, 1975 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 28)
    - Audience Statistics, 1975 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 29)
    - Bonuses, 1975 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 30)
    - Carson-Pirie-Scott Incorporated, 1975 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 31)
    - Circulation, 1975 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 32)
    - Clips: People, 1975 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 33)
    - Conventions (Dinners, Etc.), 1975 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 34)
    - Conventions: Trade, 1975 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 35)
    - Conventions: Super Market Institute: Bal Harbour, Florida: January 12-15, 1975 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 36)
    - Conventions: American Association of Advertising Agencies: Puerto Rico: March 19-22, 1975 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 37)
    - Conventions: Sour Mash: April 24-25, 1975 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 38)
    - Conventions: Energy Conference: Lyford Cay: April 24-27, 1975 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 39)
    - Conventions: National Association of Convenience Stores: September 21-25, 1975 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 40)
    - Conventions: National Association of Food Chains: Washington, D.C.: October 12-15, 1975 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 41)
    - Conventions: Western American Association of Advertising Agencies.: October 12-15, 1975 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 42)
    - Conventions: Association Of National Advertisers: Palm Beach: November 30-December 3, 1975 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 43)
    - Conventions: Lyford Cay: November, 1975 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 44)
    - Copy Acceptance, 1975 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 45)
    - Covers, 1975 (Offsite-box 2949, Folder 46)
    - Dinners: Fischbach Gallery: Brainard, Connecticut: December 15, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 1)
    - Dinners: Screenings: Fortune: May 22, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 2)
    - Distribution: Delivery, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 3)
    - Edit Film: People: Between The Covers, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 4)
    - Europe Trip: August-September, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 5)
    - Faces magazine, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 6)
    - First Anniversary Party, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 7)
    - Free Space Requests, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 8)
    - Future of Magazines, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 9)
    - Golf, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 10)
    - Hall-Kirkendall and Associates, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 11)
    - Ideas for People, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 12-13)
    - International, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 14)
    - Legal: General, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 15)
    - Legal: Logos, Other Magazines, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 16)
    - Letters: Miscellaneous, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 17)
    - Letters: Personal, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 18)
    - Magazine Publishers Association: General, 1970-1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 19)
    - Magazine Publishers Association: Magazine Day: Chicago: February 27, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 20)
    - Memoranda: Barnet, Bruce, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 21)
    - Memoranda: Corr, Joe, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 22)
    - Memoranda: Donovan, Hedley, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 23)
    - Memoranda: Hale, Paul, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 24)
    - Memoranda: Keylor, Art, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 25)
    - Memoranda: McCluskey, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 26)
    - Memoranda: Sidey, Hugh, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 27)
    - Memoranda: Stolley, Dick, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 28)
    - Memoranda: Thomas, Dick, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 29)
    - Memoranda: Valk, Garry, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 30)
    - Miscellaneous, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 31)
    - Orlando Market, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 32)
    - Permissions, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 33)
    - Personnel, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 34)
    - Photographers, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 35)
    - Positioning, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 36)
    - Presentations, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 37)
    - Price Increase: 50 Cents, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 38)
    - Promotion, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 39)
    - Publisher's Estimate, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 40)
    - Publicity: Air, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 41)
    - Publicity: Print, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 42)
    - Rates, 1975-1976 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 43)
    - Requests for Appearances from Schools, Etc., 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 44)
    - Research, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 45)
    - Result Stories, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 46)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Durrell, Dick, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 47)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Lund, Chuck, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 48)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Ochs, Mal, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 49)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Plaia, Dean, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 50)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Posthorn, Stan, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 51)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Thomas, Dick, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 52)
    - Simmons (W.R. Simmons Research), 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 53)
    - Speeches: General, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 54)
    - Speeches: Grand Rapids Ad Club: October 3, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 55)
    - Speeches: Advertising Club of Fairfield Country: September 10, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 56)
    - Speeches: Requests for: General, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 57)
    - Speeches: Requests for: Cleveland Advertising Club, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 58)
    - Time Distribution Services: Wholesaler Incentive Program, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 59)
    - Time Distribution Services and Select Marketing: Store, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 60)
    - Time Distribution Services and Select Marketing: Wholesalers, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 61)
    - Time Distribution Services Staff Memoranda: From Dick Durrell, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 62)
    - Time-Life Films, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 63)
    - Test Markets: Portland and Minneapolis-Saint Paul: 50 Cent Test, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 64)
    - Two Year Plan, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 65)
    - Weekly Reports to Art Keylor, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 66)
    - Women, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 67)
    - Young & Rubicam, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 68-69)
    - Branch Offices: Minneapolis, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 70)
    - Branch Offices: Washington, D.C., 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 71)
    - Branch Offices: West Coast: General, 1975 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 72)
    - Advertising Complaints (Reproduction), 1976 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 73)
    - Advertising Council, 1976 (Offsite-box 2950, Folder 74)
    - Airline: Subscriptions, 1976 (Offsite-box 2951, Folder 1)
    - Alberse, 1976 (Offsite-box 2951, Folder 2)
    - Associated Press, 1976 (Offsite-box 2951, Folder 3)
    - Automotive Strike: Policy, Etc., 1976 (Offsite-box 2951, Folder 4)
    - Awards, 1976 (Offsite-box 2951, Folder 5)
    - Bonuses, 1976 (Offsite-box 2951, Folder 6)
    - Budgets: General, 1976 (Offsite-box 2951, Folder 7)
    - Cambridge Research, 1976 (Offsite-box 2951, Folder 8)
    - Canada, 1976 (Offsite-box 2951, Folder 9)
    - Clips: General, 1976 (Offsite-box 2951, Folder 10)
    - Clips: People, 1976 (Offsite-box 2951, Folder 11)
    - Cole, Monger, Waterhouse, 1976 (Offsite-box 2951, Folder 12)
    - Conventions: Dinners, Etc., 1976 (Offsite-box 2951, Folder 13)
    - Conventions: Super Market Institute Midwinter: Bal Harbour: January 11-14, 1976 (Offsite-box 2951, Folder 14)
    - Conventions: Western Association of Food Chains: Coronado: April 4-7, 1976 (Offsite-box 2951, Folder 15)
    - Conventions: Building Conference: Lyford Cay: May 2-5, 1976 (Offsite-box 2951, Folder 16)
    - Conventions: National Association of Chain Drug Stores: San Francisco: May 16-19, 1976 (Offsite-box 2951, Folder 17)
    - Conventions: Food Merchandising Education Council: August 22-24, 1976 (Offsite-box 2951, Folder 18)
    - Conventions: National Association of Convenience Stores: Atlanta: September 19-23, 1976 (Offsite-box 2951, Folder 19)